{
    "subject": "resource/Ralph_Sharon",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/London",
    "human_readable": "Ralph Sharon was born in London.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9827591180801392,
            "question": "Is London the place where Ralph Sharon was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9259274005889893,
            "question": "Where was Ralph Sharon born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7366873025894165,
            "question": "What city is associated with Ralph Sharon's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6684010028839111,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Ralph Sharon's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5045599937438965,
            "question": "Could Ralph Sharon's upbringing in London have shaped his career path?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4891456961631775,
            "question": "Where might Ralph Sharon have spent his childhood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4651251435279846,
            "question": "What are some potential influences on Ralph Sharon based on his birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29119637608528137,
            "question": "What is known about Ralph Sharon's early life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2604444921016693,
            "question": "Do you have any information about Ralph Sharon's family history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16498936712741852,
            "question": "In which country is London located?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ralph Sharon was born in London.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7203_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you have any information about Ralph Sharon's family history?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7203_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is known about Ralph Sharon's early life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7203_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some potential influences on Ralph Sharon based on his birthplace?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7203_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7203_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7203_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7203_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7203_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7203_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7203_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7203_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7203_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7203_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7203_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nAll four documents contain information about Ralph Sharon's birthplace, and three of them specifically state that he was born in London. The fourth document also mentions his birthplace as Bethnal Green, which is a part of London, England. Therefore, the triple \"Ralph Sharon was born in London\" is supported by the information in the documents."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently state that Ralph Sharon was born in London, England. For example, the document at file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7203/re-ranker-msmarco/71.txt specifies \"Ralph Sharon was born on September 17, 1923 in Bethnal Green, London, England, UK.\" Therefore, the statement \"Ralph Sharon was born in London\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}